prepressure.com 2019-12-30

# Prepressure

_This privacy policy is an honest attempt to inform you about the way I collect, use or otherwise handle your personally identifiable information. It is as boring as all the other statements found elsewhere on the web and it is  unlikely to teach you anything new or be worth the time needed to read it._

### What personal information is collected from people that visit this website?

When you fill in a form to leave a comment on a page, you are asked to enter your name, email address and optional website URL. The name will be displayed within the comment to add a personal touch to the comments. Feel free to use a fake name. I recommend using a funny one. The e-mail address might be used to get in touch with you but isn’t shown to other visitors. The website URL is added as a hyperlink to your name. I frequently delete URLs for comments that I assume are posted by content spammers. The latter might also lead to the entire comment being rejected and subsequently deleted.

### How do we protect your information?

Your personal information is contained behind a secured network and is only accessible by me. The transfer of your personal data is encrypted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology.

### Does this site use ‘cookies’?

Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer’s hard drive through your web browser (if you allow) that enables the site’s or service provider’s systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.

  * I use cookies to help me compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction. This might lead to a better site experience but the data are mainly used to brag in the pub how many visitors my site got in the past year.
  * I assume the cookies from third party services are mainly used to keep track of advertisements.
  * You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser settings. Since each browser is a little different, look at your browser’s Help Menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies. If you turn cookies off, it won’t affect your user experience but it seriously limits my bragging capabilities.

###  Any third-party stuff worth mentioning?

I do not sell, trade or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information.  I may, however, release such information when this is required by the law. It would be very cool if that ever happens! Non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising or other uses. In other words: Google also gets access to the analytics and advertising related data they collect through their trackers that are used on this site. The same is likely true for the WordPress tracker that collects data that Automattic has access to.

### What about the children?

This site does not specifically target children under the age of 13 years old, unless they are really really into offset printing and like prepress software and so.

### How can I contact you?

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy, you may contact me. Please don’t. My e-mail address consists of my first name, followed by one of those curly things and then prepressure.com.

23 May 2018
